Tudor Popescu

tudor.m.p@outlook.com · +447465402934 · London SE8 · 2d0r.github.io

Summary

I am a Front-End Developer with 3 years experience building & designing web apps. Math and logic are second nature. I have a sharp eye for intuitive design. Writing and producing songs is my hobby.

Skills

(Next.js) (Node.js) SASS) (Puthon) PostgreSQL (Sketch)

Experience

Web Developer

Welam, 2022 - present

of the WeJam immersive band experience. Overhauled the UI design, improved user journeys, created new screens such as Leaderboard to add to the experience. Solved connectivity and server-messaging issues.

Trainee Developer

WeJam, 2022

Cut my teeth automating stages of the song score processing using Python and Lillypond (a music engraving language). Learnt React.js from mid-level developer through pair-programming.

Freelance Web and UX Designer

2022 - present

web, in Figma. Created and updated visual assets using Figma, Sketch and Pixelmator Pro.

Designed and implemented landing sites for various clients. I used Figma, Squarespace, Wix.

Song Production Assistant

WeJam, 2021

Prepared song scores to be processed and added to the

Projects

Kronos • 2023 - 2024

Learnt to separate client from server components. Learnt to Used Server Actions to fetch data and query the database.

2d0r Portfolio • 2024

animations, TipTap for markdown notes editor.

Wolfpack • 2023

Created responsive landing page for Wolfy's Bar NFTs using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Desgined project in Figma.

Education

Front-End Engineer • 2024

Professional Certification by Codecademy

React · Redux · JavaScript · HTML · CSS Async Functions · APIs · Testing with Mocha Algorithms · Data Structures

Product Design • LoveCircular • 2022

Computer Science College

95% Grade in the Romanian Baccalaureate

Finished top-tier college, Andrei Saguna in top 30% of class.